(Penny:)- Let's watch another one.
- Really?
(Penny:)Yeah. It was fun.
It kind of reminded me of my high school.
(Penny:)But instead of vampires,
we had meth-heads. Ahem.
(Penny:)But both came out at night
and had messed up teeth.
(Leonard:)All right, cool.
I think you'll like the next one better.
(Leonard:)All the cheerleaders
are suffering from an evil curse.
(Penny:)Oh. Well, that's like my high school too.
But instead of a curse, it was crabs. Heh.
(Amy:)I've come up with a series of exercises
to help with your compulsive need for closure.
I take issue with the word "compulsive."
(Amy:)All I'm saying is we live in a world
where closure isn't always an op...
- tion! Okay!
(Sheldon:)For the sake of argument,
let's say I have a problem.